原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨  AlgerDestiny
翻译   Stampy  二糯米  克里斯托啊托  五天
翻译   马丁马丁回音山  小饼干  小布丁
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第二十二集[本季终]
谁要爆米花
Who wants popcorn...
-我要  -我要
- Yay! - Yay!
串起来挂上圣诞树
...to string and put on the Christmas tree?
我去
Ah, damn it.
妈妈  我在主日学校做了装饰品
Mom, I made an ornament at Sunday school.
真的好
Oh, it's so...
黏糊糊
sticky.
棒冰汁儿代表了耶稣的血
The Popsicle juice represents Jesus's blood.
这个放在树后面真是太好看了
That would look so pretty on the back of the tree.
前圣诞节
在这神圣的日子想想我们的辛苦劳动
圣诞节的东西
别挂到树上
Do not put on tree.
可能会这样
May occasionally do this:
哔哔哔
Beep! Beep! Beep!
看  一顶旧圣诞帽
Ooh, look! An old Santa hat.
你知道谁会喜欢戴吗
You know who would love to wear this?
没人
No one.
狗狗
The dog!
快点丽莎  拍张照
Quick! Lisa, take a picture.
我觉得他不想拍照
I don't think he wants to take a picture.
狗狗  喜欢
Dogs... love...
人的衣服
people clothes.
你有拍到吗
Did you get a good picture?
好像没有
I don't think so.
他害怕
He's afraid of it.
没有  他没有
No, he's not.
该死  我们浪费了三张照片
Darn, we wasted three digital photos.
玩的开心吧你  小坏狗
Ugh. Well, suit yourself, spoilsport.
圣诞贺卡不放你照片了
You're out of the card!
别担心  不会那样对他的
Don't worry, he's not out of the card.
-我们能不能不出镜  -每个人都得出镜
- Can we be out of the card? - Everyone's in the card!
行吧  但别跟去年一样
Okay, but not like last year.
圣诞快乐
*叮叮当  当当叮*
*Ah, jingle bell, jingle bell*
*叮当叮当嗨嗨嗨*
*Jingle bell rock, oh*
*叮当嗨  叮嗨当*
*Jingle bell rock and jingle bell rock*
节日快乐
*嗨里个嗨  嗨上嗨*
*A-rockin' and rockin'*
*嗨完一首歌*
*And words of the song*
*看来我停在了草坪上*
*Looks like I parked on the lawn*
*跑呀  跑呀*
*Oh, giddyap, giddyap*
*跑呀  我们走吧*
*Giddyap, let's go*
*这里有槲寄生*
*There's mistletoe*
*我们要亲吻*
*There's kissin' to do*
*要亲吻好多人*
*And lots to kiss.*
给爷爷的
马姬  你绝对猜不到我给你买了什么
Marge, you're never gonna guess what I got you.
它把我的短裤吞了
It ate my shorts!
这件事实现了之后也没那么有意思
Oh, now that it's happened, it's not so funny.
老侯  我们要好好谈谈
Homie, we have to talk about the difference
礼物和家庭用品的区别
between gifts and household supplies. Hmm?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
什么事这么开...
What's all the fu...
搞什么
What the...
那条狗最好有个好理由
That dog better have a good explanation!
是我干的
I did it.
用报纸打我吧
Hit me with the newspaper.
你知道我现在都在网上看新闻
You know I get my news online.
各位
Guys...
圣诞老人的小帮手在干什么
what is Santa's Little Helper doing?
我觉得他很不对劲
I think something is very wrong with him.
我觉得我们应该带他去看狗狗心理医生
I think maybe we should take him to a dog psychologist.
狗狗心理医生
Dog psychologist, eh?
从沙发上下来  下来
Get off the couch. Get off.
下来
Get off!
爸爸  我知道你在想什么
Dad, I know what you're thinking.
不是那样的
It's not that.
知识学堂
坐下
留下
学习
和艾琳·沃尔夫共度一晚
明天晚上艾琳·沃尔夫要办一场免费的讲座
Elaine Wolff is giving a free lecture tomorrow night.
她是个传奇
She's a legend.
明天不行
Oh, not tomorrow.
明晚是终极格斗冠军赛243
Tomorrow's UFC fight 243.
你为什么那么在乎一场破格斗比赛
Why do you care so much about one stupid fight?
因为他花了60块钱去看
'Cause he paid 60 bucks to watch it.
60块钱去看一场比赛
60 bucks to watch a fight?
其实是70块  我买的高清
Actually, 70. I got it in HD.
我们都没有高清电视
We don't even have an HDTV.
我想让付费电视的运营商以为我是个大人物
I wanted the pay-per-view operator to think I was a big shot.
它在盯着那个污渍  污渍  污渍
He's staring at that smudge... smudge... smudge.
这只狗  狗  狗怎么回事
What's wrong with that dog... dog... dog?
我需要药  药  药
I need my pill... pill... pill!
三颗药片
That's three pills!
我喜欢玩糖果消消乐
I love playing Candy Crush.
爸爸  我有事和你讲
Dad, I need to tell you something,
但是悲观的来说
but I've come to the sad conclusion
我认为你理解雌性的声音会有困难
that you have difficulty hearing the female voice.
我也爱你  宝贝
Aw, I love you, too, honey.
因此  我委托巴仔替我发言
Therefore, I have deputized Bart to speak for me.
你好吗
How you doin'?
爸爸  我认为你是一位可敬的人
"Father, I believe you're an honorable man."
真的吗
Really?
好吧
Okay.
在危难关头  你
"In times of peril, you, um...
甚至  事件
even... event..."
最终
"Eventually."
终将做出正确的决定
"...eventually do the right thing,
但是圣诞老人的小帮手遇到了麻烦
"But Santa's Little Helper is in crisis,
等待你的最终觉悟恐怕为时已晚
and 'eventually' may be too late."
讲得不错  孩子
Aw. Well said, boy.
丽莎写的这个文章赢得了我最高的敬意
And, Lisa, for writing it, you win my highest honor,
一个侯默的热情拥抱
a hearty Homer hug. Mm.
现在我们放松一下
Now we party.
你为什么这样吃糖
Why do you eat candy that way?
-我已经刷过牙了  -好吧
- I already brushed my teeth. - Oh.
春田知识学院
如何调情
如何避免性骚扰的指控
如何像一位专业人士切百吉饼
晚上好
Good evening.
和狗待在一起的时间越长
"The more I spend time with dogs, the more I realize
我越能感受到与人类相比我更喜欢狗
that I entirely prefer them to people."
不  不  我是认真的
No, no, I'm serious.
我真的看不起你们
I really despise you.
看不起我们吗  我作为狗的主人
Despise us? I... Hey, as the owner of a dog,
还有老虎和海豚的主人  我被极度冒犯到
a tiger and a dolphin, I am highly offended.
极度冒犯
Highly!
好吧  首先
Okay, first of all,
我讨厌你们把自己称为主人
I hate that you call yourselves "Owners."
你拥有一个生命吗
You own living beings?
太好了
Nice.
你好
Uh, hello?
克雷顿  我现在不方便接电话
Clayton, I can't talk right now.
我离开了她
I've left her.
我离开了我的妻子
I have left my wife.
什么  真的吗
What? Really?
你我从小学起就彼此相爱
You and I have loved each other since primary school.
她知道这点
She knew that,
所以我觉得她松了一口气
so I think she was relieved.
克雷
Oh, Clay.
我都已经不抱希望了
I'd stopped allowing myself to hope.
可是  我想我得过会儿再给你回电话
But, uh... I think I got to call you right back.
别  别  别挂电话
No, no! Stay on the call.
我们正听得津津有味呢
We're invested.
我得挂电话了  我正在演讲呢
I have to go. I'm giving a lecture.
等等  等等
Wait! Wait!
我们会结婚的  是吧
We're getting married, right?
是  当然  当然  是  随便你
Yeah, sure, sure, yeah, whatever.
等等
Wait!
没错
Oh. Yes.
你们不配有狗
You don't deserve dogs!
它们嗅出你的疾病
They sniff out your diseases
在你乘飞机时安慰你
and comfort you when you ride planes.
可总有人问我  "怎么能让我的狗听话"
And I constantly hear: "How do I get my dog to listen?"
- 勒住他的脖子直到他认输  -老天
- Choke him till he taps out! - Oh, good God!
总是问狗能为你做什么
Always what can your dog do for you.
从来没有人问过我
Never once has somebody asked:
"我的狗是想表达什么"
"What is my dog trying to say?"
坏人  坏人
Bad! Bad!
你们个个都是坏人
All of you, bad!
这是我上过的最糟的辅导课
This was the worst extension class I ever took. My God.
比插花课还糟糕
It was even worse than flower arranging.
谁会知道石头花属应该放哪啊
I mean, who can say where baby's breath should go?
石竹科植物底下的一个属
反正我不知道  我就告诉你这么多
Huh. Not I. Tell you that much.
女士...
Uh, ma'am...
给我跪下
Down.
没事的  我们没有恶意
It's okay. We're friendly.
女士  我知道您曾经和我一样
Ma'am, I know you were once a young,
是一个好问的小姑娘
inquisitive girl like me.
和你可不一样
Mm, not like you, no.
我知道什么时候该保持沉默
I knew when to keep quiet.
求你了  我的狗神经崩溃了
Please. My dog is having a breakdown.
所以如果这些眼泪打动不了你...
So if these tears mean nothing to you...
帮我的狗  不然就和我干架
...help our dog, or let's do this!
拿好我的项链
Hold my pearls!
听着  我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry,
我不能
I just can't d...
妈呀
Oh, my.
可怜的小家伙
You poor boy.
你是有故事的狗子
You've got a story to tell.
能教教我们怎么做吗
Could you teach us to do what you do?
从他的视角看世界
To see the world through his eyes?
不是从他的视角
Oh, not through his eyes.
这是重点
That's the point.
狗的主导感官是嗅觉
A dog's dominant sense is smell.
他用鼻子认识世界
He sees the world with his nose,
他能闻到的比我们能看到的多得多
and his nose sees so much more than our eyes.
比如  我们看到的是路灯柱
For instance, we see a lamppost.
你的狗看到的是每一个曾经路过的人
Your dog sees everyone who's ever been here.
招募鼓手
联系奥拓
他真的很喜欢你
Hmm. He really likes you.
他崇拜我  因为知道我能帮忙
He adores me. Knows I can help him.
想让我也爱他
Wants me to love him back.
但我不行
But I can't.
一个女人只能铲有限的屎
A woman can only scoop so much poop.
停下
Stay.
做得好
Good stay.
快找到能帮我们的部分
Come on, get to the part that helps us.
《寻找好狗狗》
我尽力了  她在致谢里
I'm trying. In the acknowledgements,
感谢了所有101只斑点狗
she thanks all 101 dalmatians!
至少我能把脏帽子洗了
Well, at least I can wash this filthy hat.
坏狗狗  巨坏狗狗
Bad dog! Very bad dog!
臭狗狗
Crap dog!
丽莎  快  拿急救包来
Lisa, quick! Get the first aid kit!
我们没有急救包
But we don't have a first aid kit.
去圣诞树下找找
Look under the tree.
如果他要留在外面  我也一样
Well, if he's staying outside, I'm staying outside.
你不能留在外面
You are not staying outside!
你说了不算
You are not the boss here!
我说了算  他雇了我来对你发号施令
Well, I am, and he paid me to tell you what to do.
这个男孩要睡在外面
This boy is sleeping outside.
遵命
Yes, sir.
-我们要怎么办  -别担心  亲爱的
- What are we going to do? - No problem, sweetie.
狗狗兽医到处都是
There are a lot of dog doctors out there.
最便宜的狗狗兽医
吱吱真便宜
价格低廉的宠物护理
嘿  你们好啊
Hey. Hello.
看看这个小帅哥
Oh, look at this handsome guy.
你怎么啦  伙计
What's up with you, fella?
他咬了我妈妈
Um, he bit my mom.
我明白了  正好有人取消了预约
Oh, I see. Well, we've had a cancellation,
如果你们愿意  我们现在就可以让他安乐死
so if you like, we can just put him down right now.
-什么  -不行啊
- What?! - No!
我...我不觉得有那个必要
I-I don't think that's necessary.
不  但我觉得咬人这种事有一次就有一百次
Oh, no, I'm afraid once a biter always a biter.
除非你们能好好训练一下他
Unless you, like, train 'em or something,
但那样巨麻烦
but that's... that's crazy hard.
需要我给你们一点时间道别吗
Would you like a minute to say goodbye?
想都别想  我们走了
No way. We're leaving.
我甚至看都不想看你
And I don't even want to look at you.
我觉得我现在就像皮克斯的标志
Hmm. I feel like the Pixar logo.
我们该拿这条狗怎么办呢
What are we going to do with the dog?
我想他只能先住在我给他
I guess he's just gonna have to stay in the doghouse
盖的狗窝里了
I built for him.
你们好孩子们  兽医报告了说你们的狗会咬人
Hey-a, kids. The vet reported your dog as a biter,
所以我要在这等到动物管理的人来
so I'm supposed to wait until animal control gets here
把他带走
to take him away.
什么
What?
所以  在我们等候的这段时间里
So, uh, well, while we wait,
你们想玩"西蒙说"吗
uh, you want to play Simon Says?
西蒙说不要杀我们的狗
Simon says don't kill our dog.
我才是西蒙
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I'm Simon.
你不是西蒙
You're-you're not Simon.
爸爸  他们来抓我们的狗了
Dad! They're coming for our dog!
我不会同意的  你这个蓝色大气球
I won't let you, you... you big blue balloon.
这画面我挺喜欢  想象一下我在狂欢游行中
Ooh, I like the image. Hey, imagine me in a parade, huh?
多酷啊
Oh, boy.
该死
Oh, darn it.
你打过去告诉他们
You call them and tell them
我们是不会让你带走我们的狗的
we are not letting you take our dog.
我取消不了  软件上都显示了
I can't cancel. They're already on the app.
它说他们还有六分钟就到了  你看
It says they're six minutes away. See?
终点确认
预计到达时间  6分钟后
长青露台  742号
他们错过了一个路口
Oh, they missed a turn.
现在他们掉头了
Oh, now they're doing a U-ey.
天啊  希望他们安乐死的技术比开车好
Geez, hope this guy euthanizes better than he drives.
爸爸  快带狗狗上车
Dad, quick, take our dog
能开多远开多远
and drive as far and fast as you can.
遵命
Yes, sir.
天  太迟了
Oh, God, it's too late.
沃尔夫医生
Dr. Wolff?
我得跟你们说件事
Look, I need to tell you this one thing.
我在狗狗眼睛里看到些东西
Something I saw in your dog's eyes.
他处于崩溃边缘
He's at breaking point, and unless he has
除非有发泄口  否则情况会很糟
some kind of catharsis, something terrible could happen.
他咬了我妈
He bit my mom.
我果然是对的
It is gratifying to be right.
真是太遗憾了
Oh, how awful.
动物管理局马上就要来抓走狗狗
Animal control is coming to get him right now.
拦不住的  他们拿着带钢丝套圈的套狗棍
You can't stop them. They got sticks with wire loops.
孩子们  打包狗狗的东西
Kids, pack his things.
我带上这个  这狗得跟我走了
And I'll need this. This dog is coming with me.
我是不会空手走的
Well, I am not leaving here empty-handed.
-给我个三明治  -不
-Make me a sandwich. -No.
好吧
Okay, all right.
当个警长真逊
Being a police chief really sucks.
拿走吧
Here you go.
我给你带了饼干
Listen, I packed you some biscuits.
虽然我强烈谴责屠杀动物行为
And even though I deplore the killing of all animals,
但包里的意大利腊肠是我给你装的
when you come to the salami, it's from me.
以后谁跟我一起追松鼠啊
Now who will chase squirrels with me?
你们该走了
You better get going.
等等  虽然我不是个善于表达感情的人
Wait. I'm not an emotional guy, but...
你俩去开个狗窝房吧
Get a doghouse, you two.
犬类行为治疗研究所
看视频的时候喝点世佳水
Here. Have some Snausage water as you watch this video.
世佳  美国畅销的宠物食品品牌
研究所里没有恶犬
Here at the Institute, there are no bad dogs.
回到那个老掉牙的问题
In answer to the age-old question,
"谁是乖狗狗"
"Who's a good dog?"
是你  你是
You are. You are.
在湿枯叶里肆意吧
Relax in our pile of wet dead leaves
或在猪排掉了餐厅
or enjoy fine dining at The Dropped Porkchop.
我们保证  绝无烟花爆竹
And here's our guarantee to you: no fireworks.
你会很快舒服起来的
We'll have you feeling better in no time.
身体没有任何问题
Well, uh, there's nothing physically wrong with you,
但为建立信任  我今晚睡你窝旁边
but to establish trust, I'll sleep in your den tonight.
需要睡前给你读点书吗
Well, a little bit of, uh, reading before bed?
《每日一嚎》
犬类行为治疗研究所
"狗狗做噩梦
"Dog having nightmare,
或许与它的出身有关"
perhaps about the root of it all."
可怜的小家伙
Oh, you poor thing.
吃点安眠药  这样睡得好
Have some Lambien. It'll help you sleep.
爸  我的狗还会回来吗
Dad, am I gonna get my dog back?
当然了
Of course.
但是以防万一  我知道父亲不该
But just in case, I know this isn't the kind of thing
这么跟儿子说  不过我们来祈祷吧
a father says to his son, but let's pray.
全能的犬类守护神  圣伯纳犬
Almighty patron saint of dogs, Saint Bernard...
-我能一起吗  -当然了
- Can I join in? - Sure.
我也一起祈祷
I'll pray, too.
或许要永远失去我们的狗
Losing our dog, possibly forever,
真的让我们一家人凝聚在一起了
has really brought us together.
我不要
No!
抱歉  抱歉  我们还是祈祷吧
Sorry, sorry. Back to the prayer.
现在我要看看什么会引发你的失控
Okay, now I need to see what set you off.
对于马姬你有什么感觉
How do you feel about Marge?
她让你很舒适
She is comfort.
到底发什么了什么
So, what happened?
艾琳  你在吗
Elaine? Hello?
车来了  托斯卡纳等着我们
The car is here. Tuscany awaits.
克雷
Oh, Clay.
我应该打电话给你的
I should have called.
亲爱的  我做了一些冲动的事
Darling, I've done something impulsive.
你知道母亲一直很想让你戴她的戒指
You know how Mother always wanted you to wear her ring,
但是我们俩当时还成不了  她就过世了
but she died at a time when we had no hope.
心痛之余  我就让她和戒指一起下葬了
And in my heartache, I let them bury her with it.
这次我把她挖了出来  你愿意嫁给我吗
So I dug her up and, uh, will you marry me?
我知道"掘墓"
I know "Exhumed"
不是什么浪漫的词  但是
isn't usually the most romantic word, but...
克雷  我现在不能嫁给你
Oh, Clay. I can't marry you now.
但我过几周可以去托斯卡纳找你
But I can meet you in Tuscany in a few weeks.
我可能不会在那里
I might not be there.
我还比不过一只摇尾巴的狗吗
I can't compete with a wagging tail.
再见  克雷
Goodbye, Clay.
死人的戒指
我告诉你  我早就不爱你了
I want you to know I'm already over you.
不  别这样  不怪你
Oh, no, no, not your fault.
愚蠢的人类感情罢了  我们干正事吧
Human nonsense. Let's get back to work.
今天我想让你与大家互动一下
Today, I want you to interact with the pack.
结识几个朋友  闻闻陌生的屁股
Mingle. Sniff a butt you don't know.
有意思
Okay, interesting.
我们来深入挖掘一下
Let's explore that.
你把它埋在这里是为什么呢
You buried this here. Why?
这顶帽子是解开你心结的关键吗
Is this the key that unlocks your psyche?
汪一声代表  "是"
Bark once for "Yes," Bark twice
汪两声代表"从犬类心理学上讲不会这么简单"
for "That's too simplistic a view of canine psychology."
你好呀  这是我们的狗吗
Oh, hi. Is that our dog?
还是为了糊弄孩子找了只一模一样的
Or one that looks just like it to fool the kids?
你回来了
You're back!
这东西是哪来的
Where did this come from?
我觉得应该是从北极来的
Uh, I would have to say the North Pole?
春田商场之财产
等等爸爸  这是我们领养圣诞老人小福星那天
Wait, Dad? That was the hat I was wearing
我带着的帽子  还记得吗
the night we got Santa's Little Helper, remember?
-快  快  冲鸭  -冲鸭  圣诞老人小福星
- Go! Go! Come on, boy! - Go, Santa's Little Helper!
-快跑快跑  -快追上那只兔子
- Run! Run! - Come on! Get that rabbit!
战犬从外圈快速追近
Dog of War coming up fast on the outside...
我们能留下他吗  求你了爸爸
Aw, can we keep him, Dad? Please?
但他是个失败者  他很可悲
But he's a loser. He's pathetic.
他...
He's...
是一名辛普森
a Simpson.
原来圣诞老人小福星是一只赛犬
Santa's Little Helper was a racing dog?
不算一只合格的赛犬  跑得还没我快
Not much of one. Even I could beat him.
这下我就全搞懂了
Oh, it's all clear now.
你的狗患有创伤后精神压力症
Your dog has PTSD.
必须让他和虐待他的人对峙才行
And he has to confront his abuser,
现在立刻马上就去
and he's gonna do it right now.
其实我们正在举办节日聚餐...
Actually, we're in the middle of a holiday brunch, so...
不过我会跟你去的
But I-I'm with you.
大家再见
Uh, goodbye, everybody.
每人可以从泡芙塔上摘几个球来着
So, how many balls are we allowed of croquembouche?
看看他家有没有HBO GO频道
Let's see if they have HBO GO.
我一直想看看《迷醉》
I've wanted to watch Euphoria,
但是又不好意思在自己的电视上留下观看记录
but I'm embarrassed to have it in my viewing history.
不杀生狗舍
顺着路开就到了
是莱斯摩尔  赛狗训练师吗
Les Moore? Greyhound trainer?
-正是在下  -虐狗者
- Yeah, that's me. - Dog abuser!
能给你倒杯水泼在我脸上吗
Can I offer you a drink to throw in my face?
-好  乐意之至  -我猜也是
- Yeah, I'd like that. - Yes, I bet you would.
当然了  我只是在嘲讽
I was being sarcastic, naturally.
不是所有的驯兽师都是魔鬼
Not all trainers are monsters.
我记得这只小狗  圣诞老人小福星
Yeah, I remember this mutt. Uh, Santa's Little Helper.
没错  你们把他的名字改成什么了
Yeah! Hey, what'd you rename him?
-我们没改  -你们真够懒的
- We didn't. - Boy, are you lazy.
他生来就是同类中速度最快的之一
He was born to one of the fastest in the business,
饼干妈妈  他是她最宠爱的孩子
She Biscuit. Oh, he was her favorite.
老天  他也很爱她
And boy, did he love her.
我们就是那样知道他跑得有多快的
That's how we learned how fast he was.
所以当然  我们把他从母亲身边永远带走了
So naturally, we took him from his mother forever.
你刚刚是又扇了我一巴掌吗
Did you just slap me again?
-是我扇的  -你插队了  我还想扇呢
- That was me. - You cut the line. I want to slap.
来吧  阿麦
Here, Maggie.
-好了  我们都扇过了  -并不是
- There. Now we've all had a turn. - Not quite.
行了  我知道了
Ow! Okay, I get it.
突然之间  折磨狗的人就成了坏人
Boy, suddenly, the guy who tortures dogs is the bad guy.
他想干什么
Now what does he want?
我的老天爷
Son of a gun.
他要去哪里
Where's he going?
去找他的妈妈
To his, uh, to his mother.
我喜欢皆大欢喜的结局
Oh, I love happy endings.
*回忆*
*Memories*
*点亮了我心灵的角落*
*Light the corners of my mind*
他会没事的
He'll be all right now.
-太感谢你了  -不用谢
- Thank you so much. - Oh, you're welcome.
我得回家了  我有20只狗要遛
I better be getting home. I've got 20 dogs to walk.
要是有人帮帮我就好了
I could, uh, use some help.
好吧
Fine.
家里所有人都解决了问题  这真是太好了
It's so great everyone in this family worked out their issues.